All right we're alive.
Last...like good they're not...lash
...as...unveiling workflows...might be your...
So, I've made it this far without getting fired and now I said this is the last this is not
...of...last.
Live session of ten online for built and I was just about to
say this was your first bill that was my first bill behind the also your
...states also my lab ...I showed up hey I've got another data screw this up so this is
my boss larry seriously it is not showing you there's like a big
...cracks it on me every time so what do you guys like about
...like everything I like...live especial high library what you guys think it's out...
...it's nice.
Out of those a good scattered
And, its...on your back there.
So, you took over the...this year from.
The...my mentor man...I did I want to say I thought you
did amazing thank you thank you didn't incredible job thank you I'm very happy that
belmont found...doing this for many years and...I want
...is this the of...often that...this is the duct tape or anything
...road I'll give you ten bucks after thanks and, he's been holding onto that for ten years...going
to be fun to watch you sure...were...this up right before...have especially men all
...it...job and a whole this seriously for a long-time
but it on my dad's you have my dog eat it I mean that's...outputs
...forever so what was your favorite session so for me it was kind
of rough the first one which every snow over this guy is
...last act I mean this is the father of
...shell and they're like hey the key notes running long so go and
I was like I know a our...but I know who made it this is
...guided...the came on after it was like my god we were plan
informed to be alive so it was some last-minute a jazz that was that was by...nice-guy
on excited I did talk about...was that was kinda rocky...then afterwards
it was this all good so people being one of the big question to get is winnable everything...
oil everything...I'd love to work on it but you put me up here I'll end of
day-to-day all the sessions all channel nine lives questions will be a
...look at every bit...goes up and say that that's a good zero that's a good one that's
...right...got it so...early even looks at the video samoa
write-up as a creative...what I was doing the whole time...
Cognizant...snacks she's joining us there...so...us the switching
...switching she runs are studio when we're back...redman and then we do live events
...she's really...the buttons...we have a channel nine
...channel nine studio tour...got channel nine right now
...video dijon that like couple weeks before he left and you can show the...ever we do a
live event like this we have everyone who shows up on channel nine lives sign a big on-air
signs one of these gets hung up in our studio and the other one what goes
in my office the...skim and signature I'd like to point out believes...of
...although he the...that's...even...signature has that dude
was way cool we interviewed by the way...a class act that guy is...like
...brother, yeah.
And, then ...we have duncan mackenzie here...from
...online depth team know how to go we had it was always...idea
...measure media services for streaming...as far as now the biggest stream we've ever done
program certainly for technical content the biggest live-streaming we've ever
No, one knows if we re on.
Someone.
...content make it more hold on let me get...syrup a little bit all right
...a number of online upyeah, go ahead.
And, then you know,...everyone knows...story so in you'll still be about on channel nine
live eighty-some...you guys on.
It up I mean, you
know, in general what are the reasons that I want to come back to set seth is...be doing tell
...actually be creating content for...yeah, so, he's going to go to people's office as
...got with community get...wipe was going to be great...and...yeah, so,
whatever...dasi one-on-one make sense...email film the
...requests and I'll go to events to
interview people there I mean whoever you want to talk to or everyone is see
...tell me...like hey let's go
look big advocacy nice so you let-me know who you want me to talk to and I'll talk
...job is your proxy and then next week we pack up here hopefully
will be packed by...growing...plants...in two minutes...
get...statement on everything...the out
...and then I'll...ignite and will be live from ignite all next...
We have two hours sorry two days and eighteen hours to the
...starts in chicago and you're actually running that as well yeah, yes,...duncan
...stillI'm...I'm actually going home first and then going to...a
...my kids and then I'll go to chicago science.
And, then ...months and I go from ignite to the msr devices and networking
...paris and also be live from
there the week after ignite and then I'll go see my kids...you
...subject why you...pop-up...everyone needs to know great
...bigger it's only been five years...the rows so it's not like I don't ever,
you know, yeah, that's fine and, then how many nine guys we give out this year fifteen hundred
...on frosting under the doesn't matter how many we bring we go through all of...what
...a...amazing...alone
That is the.
...omen back on the moi.
Share on yet we also had two thousand...
I'm all right all right so
...thousand...you thousands...a thousand laptop stickers
...fifteen hundred nine...last one I ate it was the case
...all those more for eating nowthe you'll be all right I...still got this right I
...all-star that's a...by beth...for whoever's...next europe is...
And, then yeah, and, then the nine guy made in the keynote this year that's right...three-d model the
...one of the three-d models so, if you're home and you're like I wish I had a nine
guy you can get that three-d model and printed on a three-d printers so just go to channel mine right now
it's on the front-page and you can download that model it wasn't the exact model we use
...we didn't have it...better one it is a better one it's really nice them by instead of the guy who
does all of our intro videos for all the shows on channel nine.
And, if you do one of these from nine guys sent us a postcard that post with the three-d model
also has where to send a postcard to get one of the has it has his address...
...postcard you'll take care of it alas I'll take care of it by that I mean afforded to
goal nonsense nothing new...they...nobody go get it put it ebola...answer give it to
And, I think that's...that it that's the thing I'm...going...right,
yeah, there's other build wrapping up you...get a rods here for another good